It's like I'm drunk.
What?
I'm drunk now?
What? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Is this alcohol, by any chance?
Ujiro! He was a star of Bijyutsu-gaku!
The stars of Bijutsu Gaku! Please make yourself at home!
Today's members are Yuta Suzuki
Nikki Karuto, and
and Kane Uchimura!
Please help us out!
So, we are here at an unfamiliar place today!
This place is called "Okageya" in Sendai.
You all climbed the Yamadera temple the other day, didn't you?
While we were climbing, we were always being told that we were demons!
Demons?
I thought I'd do something nice for you.
Really?
We're going to split up into groups of three and visit some of the best restaurants in Sendai.
Yay!
Now, if you'll have a seat for us, we'll be on our way.
Thank you very much.
Yes!
Where is it? Where is it?
Here!
Okay, I'm coming in.
Yes!
Oh, open the door!
Excuse me!
Yes! Come in, come in, come in.
Please sit down.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, take a seat.
Sit, sit, sit.
Go ahead.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Go ahead.
Wait a minute.
What's that? Just a minute.
I was going to ask you to eat your meal.
But you're all on your way to the Budokan.
I'm not sure if I have enough social experience to go to the Budokan.
So we'll have to cancel the party for now.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm going to have you do it.
I'm nervous during this, but I hope it's okay.
at this point.
I'm fine with this.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Is that what you're saying?
It's nice to meet you, isn't it?
Wait, who are you?
I'm talking to you.
What? Like that.
Who's this?
Goodbye.
No, it's the demon. I'm an ogre.
Oni, the biggest oni.
More ogre than Yamadera.
What are they doing?
They are idols.
Idols?
Yes, they are.
Are they with you?
They are with the four subtitles.
I see.
May I have a word?
What's this?
Hold on a second. Just breathe.
You scared me.
Surprise.
Yes, sir. I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
I forgot the subtitler.
What kind of idol are you?
His name is Hinari Tohoku.
You've never heard of him?
I don't know much about idols.
That's right.
He's my friend today.
And he's my junior.
Wow.
So, I was kind of told that I don't have enough men for the application.
I'm trying to go to the hospital.
I see.
We weren't sure who was going to be there.
Ah...
So, I'm suddenly going in for a field day tomorrow.
How old are you?
You're asking this of a woman all of a sudden?
I'm 17.17.
High School Life?
3rd year
Eighteen.
How old are you?
How old do I look?
Wow, it's really something.
It's a lot of things.
Twenty-eight.
Oh, you're estimating...
Here.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Most fragile tree
Before I give you the answer, I'd like to ask you a question.
What would you like me to say your name is?
Yuna.
Yuna is a very nice person.
Compared to your daughter, Hikaru...
Compared to your daughter, Hikaru is a terrible person.
And you're right, Bubba.
He's right.
Oh, it's me.
Excellent.
Excuse me. Can I order now?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Uh...
One juice.
One orange juice.
And some calpis.
Calpis.
Four.
Yeah!
If you two aren't talking, are you at work or something?
Oh, great.
Work?
What do you do?
I like clothes.
Clothing.
You're good with your hands, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
But what is it?
I want to be a magical girl.
Hmm?
A magical girl.
Puella Magi?
That's why I'm working so hard.
I'm working on my hands.
I see.
How do I become a Puella Magi?
If you can figure it out.
I'm good with my hands.
Right? Sorry about that.
Here you go.
This is for Mr. Curry.
Are you okay?
It's just a repeat of the last surprise.
What? What is it?
What flavor?
What taste? Sour.
It's a sour surprise.
Sour surprise?
It's not very subtle.
No, it's not.
It's a very sour surprise.
Sour.
Sour Surprise to Sour Surprise.
It's so stupid.
Shitty.
I shouldn't say "sucks.
You're acting like a Japanese tubular.
I knew it!
Could this be...
Is this some kind of a surprise?
Bitter.
Hot.
He's getting away.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Help me!
I've been to the gym before, haven't I?
I've been to the gym.
I can't communicate in English.
That's why I was wondering if you could help me.
Why? Why? Why?
Let's get back to packing.
How do they make you beg?
What kind of groaning?
What kind of grope?
What kind of crooks?
How do you jiggle?
I always have a certain way.
What do you always do?
How about a good distance?
Seriously?
How's that?
It's bigger than not dating.
Let's cut the crap.
Yeah!Yay!
Then, let's get them one at a time.
Let's ask them what kind of words and what kind of tension they would like to see if they were to express their feelings.
Who would like to start?
If Hima-chan is going to do the leather
Then, let's start with you.
Then, let's start with Create.
What? Let's see...
Hmm...
I guess I'm...
Because I'm this kind of idol.
I probably can't do
I can't do the Yuzu no Kie
But...
But I'm very happy when I'm with you, so I asked you to stay with me from now on.
I'm really like this person.
That's cute.
So don't go home too much already.
You're interrupting my business.
Let's see...
I think you're in the right place next to me.
Oh, wow!
For a moment there, you might think, "What? I'm sure you'll think, "What?" But I like it.
What does that mean?
I like four-letter words.
It's a Tariki book!
It kind of becomes my hobby every time.
I don't know... I like to write a lot of four-character phrases.
I like four-character idioms now.
I put them in there.
I told them I think it's more of a help test.
If they don't know what they're talking about...
What if he/she turns back straight away?
What? I like you, you idiot.
Oh!
Wow!
Is it good?
Good!
That's good!
That's good.
So, can I introduce you?
I don't know what that is.
Well, I...
I've been an idol since I was a little girl.
I've never really been in love.
But here's what I've got.
If you like.
Buy it for the next something.
Please keep liking me.
Perfect.
Above all, it's what you promised.
It's great.
Great.
I bet you're fast.
Did you have a good working experience?
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
To be continued
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating at the end.
Please finish the post! Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
That's all for now, Uchira!
That's all for Ground Star Last, Ugidamintup.
Thank you very much.